Everybody needs a release.
Full Frontal is a comedy, romance film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
A day in the life of a group of men and women in Hollywood, in
the hours leading up to a friend's birthday party.
Gus, played by David Duchovny.
Hitler, played by Nicky Katt.
Lee, played by Catherine Keener.
Linda, played by Mary McCormack.
Carl, played by David Hyde Pierce.
Francesca / Catherine, played by Julia Roberts.
Full Frontal is a 2002 American comedy-drama film by Steven Soderbergh about
a day in the life of a handful of characters in Hollywood.
It stars Catherine Keener, Blair Underwood, David Duchovny, Julia Roberts,
Mary McCormack, Nicky Katt, Brad Pitt, and David Hyde Pierce.
The film was shot on digital video using the Canon XL-1s in under a month.
The film blurs the line between what is real and what is fiction in its
depiction of a film within a film (and possibly within another).
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.